Ahmed Hamada Mohamed

Email: enghamadafci99@gmail.com

Phone: 01127585863 Address: Giza, Egypt Date of Birth:17 /11 / 1994

Skills Summary

Junior software engineer with experience and good knowledge in the field of software development including system analysis and design, Web development, Android development, C#, asp.net, Microsoft SQL Server, Ajax, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Object Oriented Programming, Algorithms, Data Structures, C++, Java, Firebase, MySQL with an accumulative experience through several projects, and courses. Skilled at learning new concepts and techniques, working well under pressure and communicating ideas clearly and effectively.

Work Experiences

Android Developer: Giza Host Company (September 2017 – December 2017)

Web Developer: Graduation project (January 2017 – June 2017)

About tourist places in Egypt

Using Asp.net and Microsoft SQL Server

Cloud Developer: IBM (January 2017 – June2017)

Certified in Cloud Application Developer

Mastery Award (2016)

Android Developer : Google Mobile Application Launchpad (MAL) (Apr 2016 – Sep 2016)

Software development experience and Android skills development

Certified in Developing Android Apps

Mobile Developer: IBM (Jul 2015 – Oct 2015)

Certified in Cross platform

Mobile Application Developement with Worklight Studio v6.2

Projects

Next plan: Android application for company

Movie Application: Android application...

Download: https://drive.google.com/open?id=0B_YRWIj4J_vfLWRQMF8zaFF3VIE

Github:https://github.com/ahmdhamada/Movie

Aklat: Android application describes delicious meals

Download: https://drive.google.com/open?id=0B_YRWIj4J_vfRmJVakl6Qy1tNjA

Chat room: Android application using Firebase

Download: https://drive.google.com/open?id=0B_YRWIj4J_vfcXFTQ1p4MFFmdWc

Sfrny: Android application about travel office

Download: https://drive.google.com/open?id=0B_YRWIj4J_vfVnljREY1NzYzcjQ

Graduation Project: Web site about tourist places in Egypt using asp.net and SQL Server

Education

• Faculty of Computers and Information Banha University

• **B.Sc.** in Computers and Information System

(2013 - 2017)

Languages

Arabic: mother tongue. **English:** very good.